コードギアス反逆のルルーシュR2 TURN 15　C　の　世界
TURN 15　C　の　世界
The young Britannian Lelouch once swore a vow.
ブリタニアの少年ルルーシュは　かつて誓った
8年前に殺された母の仇を討ち
That he would avenge his mother,
who was killed 8 years ago.
And that he would make a world in which
his younger sister Nunnally could be happy.
妹ナナリーが幸せに暮らせる世界をつくること
For that purpose, he gained power
from the mysterious girl C.C.
そのために 彼は謎の少女C.C.から力を手に入れた
いかなる相手にでも命令を下せる絶対遵守の力 ギアス
Geass. The absolute power to
command anyone to obey him.
Lelouch used his Geass
power to embark on a path...
ルルーシュはギアスをつかい 父が統べる神聖ブリタニア帝国を破壊するべく行動をおこす
to destroy the Holy Britannian
Empire led by his father.
しかし その道の果てに 彼は何を手に入れ
But at the end of that path, what will he
have gained? And what will he have lost?
何を失うのか
明確なる定めは　ただ一つ
There is only one clear destiny.
ギアスという名の王の力を手にした者は
Those who gain Geass, the so-called
power of the king, walk a path of solitude.
孤独の道へといざなわれていく
Sekai no owari de
At the end of the world
Umareta hikari
The light that's born
Ima kaze no naka
Now blows in the wind
Kireigoto dake jaa ikirenai
Pretty words alone won't sustain you
Yasashisa dake jaa iyasenai
Kindness alone won't heal you
Ubawareta nowa nanda
What is it that was stolen from you
Kawaranai sekai de
In this unchanging world
Kikoetekita nowa nanda
What is it that you hear
Shikisai no uta
A song of color
Everything is bright...
Kudakechitta yume wo
Let our crumbled dreams resound
Asu no hate ni hibikaseru you ni
At the edge of tomorrow
Sekai no owari de
At the end of the world
Umareta hikari
The light that's born
Bokura hitotsu ni
Becomes one with us
Ima kaze no naka
Now blows in the wind
THE Cs' WORLD
久しいな　ルルーシュ
It's been a long time, Lelouch. My son.
我が息子よ
8年前の質問に答えてもらう！
Answer the question I asked you 8 years
ago! Why didn't you protect mother?!
なぜ母さんを守らなかった！？
他の皇族たちが母さんを疎んじていることを知りながら！
Even knowing how the other
members of royalty ostracized her!
人は平等ではない
People are not equal.
What?!
何っ？！
おまえはほかの者にはない力
You have Geass, a power
which no one else possesses.
ギアスを持っている
Use that power to get the answer from me!
その力で聞き出せばよかろう
誘っている
He's baiting me.
Inviting me to use my Geass on him.
俺にギアスをつかわせようと
しかし　俺がヤツの目を見るということは
But if I look into his eyes,
he'll be able to look into mine!
あいつも俺を見るということ
やつのギアスは 俺と同じ相手の目を見てかけるタイプ
His Geass is the same type as mine,
requiring eye contact.
俺が見た瞬間に　あいつのギアスが
The moment I look, his Geass, the power
to control memory, will be cast on me!
記憶をあやつるギアスがとんでくる
どうすれば
What do I do?!
What's wrong? Are you not my son?
Not a prince of Britannia?
どうした？それでもわしの子か？ブリタニアの皇子か？
This is no time to choose tepid commands!
ぬるい命令を選んでいる場合じゃない！
そうですゼロの命令です
That's right! It was Zero's orders!
すべての施設が捜索範囲
Search through all of the facilities!
Obey Zero's orders!
ゼロの命令に従い　死体はすべて指定区画に集めてください
Gather all of the dead in the designated area.
ブリタニアの実験兵がいるか 検証します
We're going to verify if any of the Britannian
experimental soldiers are among them.
This is... a massacre!
こんな?虐殺
バトレー
Bartley... I hated you for
reconstructing me with this body.
私をこのような体に改造した憎むべき男だが
but your loyalty to the imperial
family was genuine.
君の皇族に対する忠義は本物であった
Then I will make up my mind!
ならばこそ　私は決意しよう
君を尊敬すると！
I will honor you!
Lelouch vi Britannia commands you!
ルルーシュ ヴィ ブリタニアが命ずる
貴様は　死ね！
DIE!!!
よかろう
Very well, then.
勝った？
I won?
勝った
I won.
ナナリー　母さん
Nunnally... Mother...
俺は 俺は
I... I...
うおぉぉぉぉ～～！
ルルーシュのことは知らない！
I don't know anything about Lelouch!
How many times do I have to say that?!
何回いったらわかるのよ！
シャーリーの亡骸に誓って そう言えるのか
Would you swear
that on Shirley's remains?
Now, you're going to tell me everything.
With this Refrain!
話してもらうすべてこのリフレインで
Don't.
Please, don't! STOP IT!!!
やめて　やめてよやめてったらあ！
恐がらなくていい
You don't have to be afraid.
君はすぐに自分の意志を失い
You'll lose your will soon and
then you'll answer my questions.
僕の質問に答える
Big brother...
お兄ちゃん
Now, you will
obey my commands...
従ってもらう 命令に
I... I... I WILL NOT BE LIKE HIM!
俺は あいつのようには！
直接あうのは何年ぶりだったかなV.V.
How many years has it been since
we were together face to face, V.V.?
私は結局 私の定めから逃れられなかったよ
In the end, I couldn't run away
from my destiny, could I?
定めは 僕が　ひきうけるよ
I will shoulder... this destiny...
The destiny of immortality...
不死のさだめを
これは V.V.おまえ
What's? V.V., are you?
So please, Charles...
だからさ シャルル
So, do you swear it?
これは誓いだよ
うん
Yes. In this world full of lies...
この嘘だらけの世界で
僕たちだけは嘘はつかない
We alone will never lie to each other.
だって 僕は　お兄さんだから
Because...
I am... your big brother...
殺してしまった
I killed him. It was so easy.
こんなにもあっさりと
ききたいこともあった
There were things I wanted to ask him.
People I wanted to make him apologize to! Now!
わびさせたい人がいたなのに
ほお～誰に
Oh? To whom?
こしゃくだなルルーシュ！
You're an impudent child, LELOUCH!
You're alive?! Impossible!
You shot your own heart!
生きている？！そんな！確かに心臓は
策略　奸計　奇襲
Schemes, plots, surprise attacks...
そのような小手先でわしを倒そうとは
You really thought you could
defeat me with those cheap tricks?
Come at me as a true king would!
If you wish to inherit the power of the king!
王道でくるがいい
王の力を継ぎたいのであれば！
死ね～～！
DIE!!!
You call that the path of royalty?!
それが王道か！！
ギアスがきかない？
My Geass isn't working!
わからんのか ルルーシュ
Don't you understand, Lelouch?!
はやわしには剣でも銃でも
I am beyond the power
of guns or swords!
No matter what you use
against me will be USELESS!
何をもってしても
無～駄～！！
Charles, why steal V.V.'s Code now?
シャルル なぜ今になってV.V.のコードを奪った？
なぜあれだけ慕っていた兄を殺した？
Why would you kill the older
brother you loved so much?
V.V.　お前さ マリアンヌのこと 好きだったんだろう
V.V....
You loved Marianne too, didn't you?
あの男が不老不死に？
He's become immortal, too?!
勝てない 勝てるはずがない！
I can't win.
There's no way I can win!
I've gained a new power
in the place of Geass.
わしはギアスの代わりに新たなる力を手に入れた
ゆえにルルーシュ
And so, Lelouch, I shall now show you.
The true nature of this world!
おしえてやってもよい
この世界のまことの姿を
な なんだ？これは！
What is this?!
千草
Chigusa.
それは私が記憶をなくしていたときの名前
That was the name you called me
when I had lost my memory.
本当の名前は
My real name is...
ヴィレッタ
Villetta.
But to me, you'll always be...
でもおれにとっては
私はブリタニアの男爵
I am a baron of Britannia.
たとえどんな理由があろうと
No matter what the reason, if I don't erase
the disgrace of my having loved an Eleven,
イレヴンとの汚点は消し去らなければ
この世界で生きてはいけない
I won't be able to live in this world.
I suppose not.
そうだよな
どうせなら　日本で死にたかった
If it has to be this way,
I wished I could have died in Japan.
殺されるとしってここにきたのか
You came here knowing
I was going to kill you?
死ぬ時ぐらいは自分で選びたいから
Because if I have to die,
I want to at least choose when it'll happen.
You could also
kill me if you wanted to.
私を殺すという手だってあるはずだ
Why did a terrorist even save
a Britannian soldier in the first place?!
そもそもなぜテロリストがブリタニア軍人を助けた！
最初はゼロの情報をききだそうと思った
At first, I thought I could
get information about Zero from you.
君をだまして監視して
I tricked you,
kept you under surveillance...
でも 君と暮らすうちに
But, while we lived together...
I'm the enemy!
私は敵だぞ！
But I still love you!
でも好きなんだ！
ばかか 貴様は
Are you insane?!
Yes, you're the enemy.
Yes, it may be crazy...
敵だけど バカみたいだけど
でも 君を好きになってしまったんだ！
But I've fallen in love with you!
であわなければよかったんだ！
I wish I'd never met you!
ち 諜報部の
You!
From the intelligence division!
What is Geass?!
What are you up to?!
ギアスとはなんだ？
貴様は何をたくらんでいる？！
How strange.
おかしなことよ
A child who's covered with lies
desires the truth from others.
嘘にまみれた子どもが人には真実を望むか
What?
何？
What has the lie called Zero which
you wear as a mask gotten you?
おまえはゼロという仮面のうそで何を得た？
手に入れた！
It's gotten me plenty! An army which
an ordinary student could never have!
ただの学生では到底手に入れられない軍隊を！
部下を！領土を！！
Followers! Territory!
You lost Euphemia.
ユーフェミアを失った
スザクやナナリーにも姿をさらせない
You can no longer see
Suzaku or Nunnally!
黙れ！
Be quiet! People lie to everyone in
order to live! I only did what others do!
人は誰でも嘘をついて生きている！
俺もそうしただけだ！
なぜ嘘をつく？
Why do you lie when you want
others to understand your true self?
本当の自分を分かってほしいと思ってるくせに
そう望みながら自分をさらけだせない
But even as you desire it,
you don't expose yourself.
仮面をかぶる
You wear a mask.
Are you afraid of others
knowing what you really are?
本当の自分を知られるのが怖いから
You're wrong!
ち 違う！
There's no need to tell lies.
嘘などつく必要はない
The reason being that you
are me and I am you.
なぜならお前がわしで　わしがおまえなのだ
It's true. In this entire world,
there is really only a single person.
そう 人はこの世界に一人しかいない
過去も未来も人類の歴史上 たった一人
In the past and the future,
in all of human history, only one.
One? What are you talking about?
一人？何をいっている？
Charles.
シャルル
遊びの時間は終わりだ
Play time is over.
私にとってそれにもう価値はなくなった
There's nothing in it for me now.
C.C.?
C.C.？
それを籠絡して私を呼ぶ必要もない
You don't have to cajole him
like this to call me here.
私はすでに　ここにいる
I already exist here.
True enough, C.C.
I shall grant your wish, then.
そうだな C.C.
おまえの願いはわしがかなえてやる
You know what C.C.'s wish is?!
C.C.の願いを知っているのか？
ルルーシュ
Lelouch... It's time you knew
the conditions of our contract.
今こそ契約条件を 我が願いを明かそう
And what my wish is.
我が願いは死ぬこと
I wish to die.
私の存在が永遠に終わることだ
To end my existence forever.
End it? But, you're!
終わる？
しかし　おまえは
In the final stage of Geass, the user attains the
position of the one who granted them the power.
ギアスの果てに 能力者は力を授けた者の地位を継ぐ
つまり　私を殺せる力を得る
In other words,
you gain the power to kill me.
To... kill you?
C.C.を 殺す？
Not one of the many people I made
contracts with ever reached that point.
あまたの契約者は　誰ひとりとしてそこまでたどりつけなかった
しかし ここに達成人 シャルルがいる
But now we have Charles here,
who has done it.
ばかな おまえは死ぬためにおれと契約したというのか？
This can't be! You made your contract
with me so that you could die?!
Correct.
そうだ
死ぬために生きてきたと？
You were living just so
that you could die?
That is where the providence
of this world lies.
この世の節理は　そこにある
限りあるもの それを命と呼ぶ
Life is defined by its limits.
違う！生きているから命のはず！
That's wrong!
We call it life because we're alive!
It's the same thing.
We can acknowledge life because death exists.
同じことだ
死があるから 人は　生を自覚できる
言葉遊びだろう そんなものは！
That's just wordplay!
Even so, people do die.
しかし 人は死ぬ
だととしても
Then what's the reason people are
born into this world?! The meaning!
この世に生まれた理由が 意味が！
You know perfectly well!
Those things are just illusions.
知っているくせに
そんなものは ただの幻想だと
死ぬだけの人生なんて哀しすぎる！
Living just to die is
too sad to even consider!
死なない積み重ねを人生とは言わない
Endless accumulation of it without
death can't be called a life.
それはただの経験だ
That's just experiences.
おまえに生きる理由があるのなら私を殺せ
If you have a reason for living,
then kill me.
Do that, and you'll be Charles's equal.
You will gain the power to fight.
そうすればシャルルと同等の戦う力を得る
さようなら　ルルーシュ
Farewell, Lelouch.
おまえはやさしすぎる
You're just too kindhearted.
待て おまえは！
Wait! You're...
やめろ！
シャルル
Charles, why did you
steal V.V.'s Code?
なぜV.V.のコードを奪った？
Is there any point
to asking questions now?
質問に意味があるのか？これから死に行くというのに
After all, you're about to die.
I suppose not.
そうだったな
では
サイタマゲットーの再開発はこちらのスケジュールですすめさせていただきます
Well then, I'll have the redevelopment of the
Saitama ghetto proceed according to our schedule.
待ってください
Wait, please.
はあ？
手を
Give me your hand.
なにか
Is something wrong?
この計画 イレヴンの皆さんに　不利益はないのですか
This plan won't disadvantage
any of the Elevens, will it?
無論ですこれは双方にとってベストな選択です
Of course not.
This is the best choice for both sides.
That's... A lie, isn't it?
それは うそですね
Please rework
the plan once more.
もう一度 この計画をみなおしてください
イレヴンの人たちにも 不利益がないように
I don't wish the Elevens to be
disadvantaged in any way.
ナナリー様実務は私ども専門家におまかせください
Princess Nunnally, please let experts like
me handle the practical matters of state.
Miss Lohmeyer! I...
I believe that I am the viceroy here!
ミス ローマイヤ
総督は私です
こうなったら　直接ルルーシュにあってたしかめるしかない
After all this, my only choice is to
confront Lelouch about this directly!
スザク政庁の仕事はいいのか？
Suzaku, are you all done with your
work at the government bureau?
ルルーシュは？中？
Have you seen Lelouch?
Well, it looks like what happened
to Shirley really shook him up.
シャーリーの件がこたえてるみたいでさ
ずっと帰ってこなくて 学校にも
He hasn't been home since,
or at school.
ルルーシュ ランペルージはどこにいる？
Where is Lelouch Lamperouge
right now?!
特に異常はありません
There's nothing
out of the ordinary.
どこだときいている？
I'm asking where he is! Where's Commander
Villetta?! Or his little brother Rolo?!
ヴィレッタ隊長は？
弟役のロロは！
ですから 報告すべき異常はありませんが
As I said, there's nothing
unusual worth reporting.
Same as always.
いつもどおりですよ
そうか 機密情報局全員に
I see... The entire O.S.I.
staff has been!
Holy Britannian Empire
DALLAS RESEARCH CENTER
すまなかったねナナリーとも話していたので
Forgive me. I had to talk to Nunnally.
It's all right.
We're not ready to start yet.
いえこれからですから
なんだったですか？
What happened?
You know the subject.
Lloyd's Camelot group and Suzaku's...
例のあれさ
ロイドたちのキャメロットとスザク君の
No, Highness,
I meant with the Tromo Agency.
いえ トロモ機関の件です
That... depends on
the results of today's test.
それは 今日の結果次第かな
Yes. My big brother Schneizel
contacted me from the homeland.
ええ 本国のシュナイゼル兄様から連絡が
エリア11は衛星エリアに昇格できそうだって
It looks like we'll be able to raise
Area 11's status to satellite area.
治安の安定と生産率の向上が認められたんですって
He said it's in recognition of the stabilized
public order and higher productivity.
それは良い知らせですね
That's good news.
Lelouch must have been Zero all this time.
やはりルルーシュはゼロだった
だが皇帝陛下に連絡したらナナリーはどうなる？
But if I report that to the emperor,
what will happen to Nunnally?
もしルルーシュの記憶が戻ることがあればナナリーはわしがつかう
If Lelouch regains his memories,
then I shall use Nunnally.
スザクさん何か隠し事でも？
Suzaku, you aren't hiding
anything from me, are you?
Of course not. You're the one
person I'd never lie to, Nunnally.
まさかナナリーにだけは 嘘はつかないよ
Then will you tell me who it was I
spoke on the phone with that time?
では いつぞやの電話のお相手をおしえていただけますか
お兄様だったのではないのですか？
Wasn't it my big brother?
スザクさん
Suzaku, you're just like him,
aren't you? Like big brother...
あなたも同じなんですねお兄様と
いない？ゼロが？
He's gone? Zero's gone?
はい対象を発見したとのコールはあったのですが
Yes. I tried to call him to say we'd sighted the
target, but he and the Shinkirō are both gone.
蜃気楼ともども
いない 兄さんが
He's gone? Big brother is?!
Where am I?
ここは
お おい！
Wha? Hey!
It's no use.
ムダよこれは私の記憶
These are my memories.
You can't interfere.
干渉はできない
C.C....
No. You're not, are you?
C.C.  いや 違う？
あなたは　誰？
Who are you?
ルルーシュだお前の
Lelouch. I'm your...
あなたに生きるための意味はあるの？
Do you have a reason to live?
I... I don't know.
But I don't want to die!
わかりません
でも 死にたくないんです！
Then let's make a contract
with each other.
では 契約をしましょう
生き延びる力をあなたに授けましょう
I will give you the power
to let you survive.
In return, will you agree to
grant me my one wish someday?
その代り　いつの日か私の願いをひとつだけかなえていただけますか
Is this?
まさか
Yes. I made a contract with her.
やめろ！やめてくれ！ふたりとも！たのむから！
Stop it! Stop it, both of you!
Please!
良い関係が築ければと思っていましたが残念です
I'm sorry about this.
I thought we might one day be friends.
やめろ！
Stop it!
扇！
OHGI!
私に発現したギアスは愛されること
The Geass manifested to me
was to make people love me.
愛？
Love?
心の奥底で　私は
Because, deep in my heart, I...
私は誰かに愛されたかった
I wanted to be loved by someone.
願いはかなったわ
And my wish was granted.
ギアスのおかげで私はあらゆるものに愛された
Thanks to my Geass,
I was loved by everyone.
でも 愛されすぎて
But I was loved too much, and in the
process, forgot what true love really was.
そのうち本当の愛がわからなくなった
私が信じたのは彼女だけ
The only person I believed in was her.
ギアスにかからない彼女は
Because my Geass couldn't work on her,
she would scold me for playing all the time.
遊んでいた私をしかってくれたから
なのに
But even so...
Right, right. I gave back all the
gifts I took, like you told me to.
はいはい言われたとおりもらいものはすべて手放しました
でもしかたないでしょう？ギアスのせいなんだから
But it can't be helped, can it?
It's the Geass's fault.
シスターには感謝してるけど 正直私も困ってるの
I'm grateful to you Sister, but to be
honest, this is a pain for me, too.
プレゼントやプロポーズにはもうあきあき
I'm so tired of all the
presents and proposals.
教主様っていう人まででてきちゃって
Now some people want
to start a religion around me!
Then shall we end this?
じゃあおしまいにしましょう
え
私の永遠を終わらせえるためには
I have to have somebody take my place
so that eternity can finally end for me.
誰かを身代わりにしなければならないの
一定以上のギアスを持つ誰かを
Someone who possesses
a Geass beyond a certain level.
どれだけ苦しかったか
Have you any idea
how difficult it's been?
生き続けるという地獄が
The hell of living on and on?
Um, what are you talking about?
あの 何の話？
残念でしたあなただまされちゃったの！
I'm sorry, dear!
I'm afraid I tricked you!
私の存在は彼女にとって
My existence for her was merely
as a tool to let her end her own life.
自分自身のピリオドを打つための道具
ただ　それだけだった
That's all it was.
あなたはまだここにいない
You're still not in here.
私にとってあなたは過去ではなく
You're not from my past.
You're a real person, aren't you?
現実の人なのね
さあ どうなんだろうな
Am I?
I couldn't really say.
よっぽど大事な人なのかしら？
I wonder if you're
very important to me.
That's impossible.
ありえないよ
そう？ここにおくってきたということは
Oh? The fact you
were sent here...
ひと時でも何かからあなたを守ろうとしたんだと思うけど
means I was trying to
save you from something.
私を憎む人も　優しくしてくれた人も
The people who hated me,
the ones who were kind to me...
All of them eventually
vanished in the flow of time.
すべて時の流れの中に消えていった
In the endless flow of time...
果てることのない時の流れの中で
だがその苦しみの日々も
But now, those days of torment...
Yes. Now it ends.
My long journey...
これで終わる 私の長い旅も
C.C.！！
C.C.!
開いたのか？ルルーシュ思考エレベーターを
You've opened it, Lelouch!
The Thought Elevator!
Now I understand! This area of space
itself is a system for disrupting thought!
なるほどこの空間そのものが
思考に干渉するシステムか
Soon it will be over.
すぐに終わる
ルルーシュよそこでみておれ
Lelouch, sit where you are and watch!
やめろ！そいつは俺の 俺の
Stop it! She's my... My!
答えろ C.C.！
Answer me, C.C.!
なぜ俺と代替わりして死のうとしなかった？！
Why didn't you try to die by
making me take your place?
You could have forced me to
accept the hell of eternal life!
俺に永遠の命という
地獄をおしつけることだってできたはずだ！
Did you pity me, C.C.?!
俺を憐れんだのか？！C.C.！
Don't die looking like that!
When death comes, die smiling!
そんな顔で死ぬな！
最後くらい笑って死ね！
必ず俺が笑わせてやる！
I promise, I'll make you smile!
So, please!
だから！！
どういうつもりだ？C.C.！
What do you think you're doing, C.C.?!
これ以上奪われてたまるか！
You think I'll let you steal any more from me?!
なんたる愚かしさか！！！
Does your foolishness know no bounds?!
俺は知っているぞ　C.C.！
I know now, C.C.! What your Geass
was! What your true wish is!
お前のギアスを！
本当の願いを！
おい！こっちをむいてくれ！
Come on! Turn towards me!
プレイヤの作動を確認
Activation of F.L.E.I.J.A., confirmed.
爆発より3秒が経過　各戦艦は報告せよ
やった
It worked. I can't believe the
explosive force generated!
まさか これほどの威力だなんて
Congratulations, Chief!
チーフ おめでとうございます
Oh, no. This is the result of
the entire staff at Invogue.
いえ インヴォーグのスタッフ全員の成果です
You should be proud, Nina.
You are a genius.
ここは誇りに思うべきだよ ニーナ
君は天才だ
光栄ですシュナイゼル殿下
I'm honored, Prince Schneizel.
ここから先 人類は 戦争は変わります
Now mankind... War itself will change!
うむこれで ダモクレスが
Now can come Damocles!
おい 戻ってきたんだC.C.
Hey! We've come back, C.C.!
Wake up!
しっかりしろ
ロロには連絡を入れた
I've contacted Rolo.
We'll use him to get out of here soon.
あいつをつかってすぐにでも
Um, who are you, sir?
あの どなたでしょうか？
何いってるんだ？
What are you talking about?
Anyway, about the emperor and that system...
それより 皇帝とあのシステムは
Are you my new master?
新しいご主人さまですか？
え？
できるのは料理の下ごしらえと掃除
I can help prepare food
for cooking and can clean.
I can fetch water and tend
cows and sheep. And sew.
水汲みと 牛と羊の世話　裁縫
文字は少しならよめます
I can read a little and
I can count to twenty.
数は２０まで
And... I can also tend
corpses, if you wish...
あ 死体の片づけもやっていましたから
Dakuse wa oni
This corrupt world is filled with demons
Seigi wa nanzo to
What is justice?
Tou mae ni aragae yo
Resist, don't just question
Akutoku no hana
The flower of evil
Gizen no yume
Dreams of hypocrisy
Mishi me niwa me wo sashi
Give your gaze to the eyes that see them
Sei mo ja mo wakatareru koto nashi
The line between right and wrong cannot be known
Hikari wa tae taiji no you ni
Light is gone, and you slumber
Kimi wa nemuru yami no shikyuu
Like an unborn child in the womb of darkness
Kodoku koso itooshii
Isolation is what you love
Yui-itsu no mikata to naru darou
It will probably be your only ally
Hitori hitori chishio ni mamire
One by one, stained with the tide of blood
Kono jidai ni umare ochita
You were born into this era
Erabareshi oujira yo
Oh, chosen princes
Tatakai koso shukuen
Battle shall be your banquet
Aa ware wa uruwashii zenchi
Oh, I am graceful omniscience
Ai no haha
The loving mother
Kimi wo umu
Who bore you
Kono chichi ni hagukumishi mono wa
The ones who were raised on my breast
Jigoku no harakara
Are your brethren in hell
Mokushi no in
The mark of apocalypse
Shinri wa nanzo to
What is truth
Shirimosezu uzumoreshi intoku no tane
A seed of secrecy buried where no one knows
Moroha no ken
A double-edged sword
Nuku ha niwa ha wo muke
Turn its blade upon the unsheathed blade
Mamorubeki mono dake wo shinjite
Believe only in what you must protect
Aru ga mama ni kimi wa
And in your own way
Kimi wo hanate
You'll set yourself free
ナナリー救出の策はある　問題はタイミングだけだ
Kallen has been captured, Shirley has
died, and now I've lost C.C. as well!
万全を期すならば　超合衆国が必要となるが
Even so, this is no time for me
to drown in sentimentality!
それは皇帝があの空間に置き去りになっていることが絶対条件
I have a plan to rescue Nunnally.
The problem is timing when to strike.
しかし
Even if we move to rescue her now,
there are too many uncertain
elements waiting in the aftermath.
To make certain it works,
I'll need a United Federation of Nations.
And for that, keeping the emperor in that parallel
space will be an absolute condition to clear.
But!
UNITED FEDERATION OF NATIONS
RESOLUTION NUMBER ONE